✔ transient Windows rename locks retry without deleting the existing store (5.5085ms)
✔ permanent write failure preserves the previous store and propagates failure (1.9672ms)
✔ a certificate with a real final_project object no longer throws on the Postgres write boundary (4.7932ms)
✔ final_project round-trips exactly through write then read (3.0936ms)
✔ a null final_project (the common case - most certificates have no capstone snapshot) stays null both ways (0.8407ms)
✔ concepts (a real Json column) is unaffected by the final_project fix - still passed through as-is (0.562ms)
✔ drafts isolate accounts, tasks and languages and preserve an explicit empty draft (7.5426ms)
✔ an older delayed save cannot overwrite a newer draft (1.9165ms)
✔ storage failures and unauthenticated persistence are reported (0.9619ms)
✔ gemTotalsByUser() matches totalGemsForStudent() for every user, across all four gem sources (2.4123ms)
✔ each required assessment must pass its own configured threshold (3.0728ms)
✔ independent attempts preserve old work and grades, deduplicate requests, isolate owners (8.1223ms)
✔ retry bound and interrupted-worker recovery (1.8297ms)
✔ worker unavailable, durable-write failure, success, and timeout contracts (19.0331ms)
[registration mail] challan failed for registration 1: Email provider did not accept the message.
✔ only a published paid offering has an authoritative fee (1.4496ms)
✔ skipped/rejected mail remains failed and retry is recoverable (3.9987ms)
[registration mail] challan failed for registration 1: synthetic storage failure
✔ concurrent requests and a retry after provider acceptance send once (11.1989ms)
✔ a durable queue write must succeed before contacting the provider (1.4469ms)
✔ course files and submissions require membership or assigned staff (9.2416ms)
✔ private identity, contract, extra submission and payment files stay scoped (2.5251ms)
✔ department attachments are limited to recipients and department managers (5.2767ms)
✔ only explicit published event resources are public; unpaid entry cannot read paid material (2.2693ms)
✔ unknown files, resume bypasses and ambiguous paths are denied (1.2751ms)
✔ password recovery and admin reset invalidate previously issued sessions (2.757ms)
ℹ tests 24
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 24
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 729.8495
